Creation of the front end for the neuro analysis workflow project. 

Overall construction: 
-  Main page: drag and drop style canvas with a toolbar on the side and another navbar for performing operations
-  -   Ability to connect the workflow operations together with arrows etc.
-  Workflow creation page: after generate workflow has been pressed, we generate a preview of the workflow which the user can then save or run
-  Running page and output page: once we have the ability to run the generated workflow
